Thank you for watching!
Stop!!
Cool.
Delicious.
It's totally new experience.
The face of ambassador meeting,tezza
It's started! The best egg rice in my
life!
Egg rice is delicious, right?
We've come up with a recipe that will
make it the best in your life.
We'll eat it this time.
The best egg rice in my life!
First, we'll put in the white vinegar.
White vinegar rice is good.
Add sesame oil and sesame seeds.
Sesame, sesame.
I thought of it, but I shouldn't say it
because it's egg rice.
Add salt.
I like to add salt to egg rice.
Soy sauce and mentsuyu are usually
added.
What is that?
That's a meringue.
It's egg white.
Kanami, you made it look professional.
It looks like cotton candy.
The white vinegar is hidden.
I hide it.
Hide the white vinegar?
Make a hole here.
Put it in the hole.
Soy milk!
It looks delicious!
It looks like a butter grill.
It looks like a delicious dish for
Instagram.
It's done.
What's the title?
It's a rice with egg yolk and tomato
sauce.
You're good at it.
I'll break it.
It's a bomb.
It's good.
I want to be born again.
It's good!
I want everyone to try this!
This deliciousness!
How is it?
It's good!
It's good, right?
The sesame oil and salt...
And this...
It's good!
Is it good?
I did it!
It's a little bit...
Fluffy!
It's a new feeling.
Sesame oil is good.
Sesame oil.
You ate it!
The sesame is really good.
Sesame. Real sesame.
It's really good.
It's good!
A new world has opened up.
I'm going to make a revolution to TKG.
I'm going to make Namul-style egg rice.
I like Namul made of bean sprouts.
I'm into it.
When I think of egg, I think of
bibimbap.
I'm going to make Namul-style bibimbap.
I made spinach with noodle soup.
I'm going to put bean sprouts and
kimchi.
When you lick the bean sprouts, rice
will be gone.
And it will be like a soap bubble.
Yes, it will be like a soap bubble.
I'm going to mix eggs.
Oh, you are going to mix them.
I'm going to put eggs.
I'm going to put kimchi.
Haru is a noodle soup lover.
It's really delicious.
And sesame seeds for finishing.
It's done.
It looks like a bibimbap.
The taste is...
Amazing!
The taste of the egg is amazing.
The noodle soup is also good.
It's really good.
It's my first time to eat the noodle
soup of Nobu.
It's good.
The ingredients are very crispy and the
warm rice goes well with it.
It's delicious.
If you love, shake up, shake up, shake
a lick, shake up.
The goal is weight, apple, and
succubus.
Lose weight, lose weight, lose weight,
and lose weight.
Don't be afraid of the future.
Next, I'm going to make a chili sauce.
Please subscribe to my channel.
You've been mixing it for a long time.
I'm going to make a chili sauce that
makes you feel excited.
I'm going to make it softer than
cannamel.
It's a soft-tasting meringue.
I'm going to add sesame oil.
You're going to add sesame oil?
I mixed it.
I'm going to mix it.
It's delicious.
It's beautiful.
It's like clouds are on the cake.
I'll put the egg on the cake.
Dore! Dore!
I like soy sauce, soy sauce, and salt.
I think everyone can drink it.
It's colored.
I'll put Korean seaweed on it.
I like it.
Korean seaweed.
It's cute.
Red.
I did it.
I'll put Korean seaweed on it.
Four.
It's a big one.
I put it on.
It looks good.
The egg is hidden.
Are you hiding the egg?
I'm hiding the egg.
The seaweed smells good.
It's like a black bowl.
I put it on.
I see.
It's a big one.
She got turn on her face
How do I look?
Thank you for watching.
It's good.
The Korean seaweed is a little soft.
It's a little soft.
It's good to eat it crispy.
But it's delicious.
Korean seaweed and rice go well
together.
I know.
Do you sometimes eat it just like that?
It's a little salty.
I put too much.
It's better to eat it now.
It's delicious.
Korean food and omelet are definitely
the best.
It's salty.
But it's delicious.
I think Korean food has a good taste.
Let's eat!
I like the texture of the chicken.
Me, too.
It's soft and has a good texture.
It's good.
Everyone's cooking is good.
Everyone's cooking is good. What should
we do?
It's good.
Do we have to decide?
We have to decide.
Now that we've all eaten,
we'll make a judgment.
A judgment.
We'll make a judgment.
With one hand?
With a finger.
You can choose your own.
We have a judge.
Everyone will be able to decide.
Everyone, please point to the best TKG
you've ever had.
One, two.
Den.
It's embarrassing.
The one who suddenly shined is...
Kanamin.
Kanamin's...
I'll wrap you in my arms.
It's a relaxing egg rice.
Thank you.
It's soft.
It was delicious.
The meringue was amazing.
I'm glad you did your best.
I'll buy this.
You were a professional.
My face is...
I'm serious.
I'm getting faster.
Everyone, please eat a lot of rice with
the best TKG in your life.
Everyone, please try this.
Please compare it.
The soup is delicious, too.
Please try it.
Life's last egg rice bowl
I want to eat it
I can do anything
Please subscribe to my channel!
I was really happy to be able to get
the second place with everyone.
I want to continue to live in a good
way until the future of Nakano Sunplaza.
We want to live with a good atmosphere.
We will definitely show you a more
cooperative appearance than last year.
We are sorry that we can't do anything
because of the support.
Our victory story has just begun.
I think that there is no such thing as
a possibility.
If we are with the members, we can
definitely make a big wall into a small
wall.
We believe in that.
So, please wait for us, Nakano
Sunplaza!
Thank you!
I'll show you how to bloom, a big
flower petal
I'll run through it recklessly, always
I'll keep carving the meaning deep in
my heart
It's really over, everyone, everyone,
it's about to collapse
I can't do it. Who decided it?
Doesn't it hurt?
It looks like it's numb, but it feels
good.
It's not painful.
It doesn't hurt.
Thank you for watching.
If you're in love, shake up, shake up,
shake a lick, shake up
I'm aiming for the weight, I'm carrying
an apple
Lose weight, lose weight, lose weight
Don't let your guard down
Let's go, do me, do me, yo
Do me, do me, yo
Don't show me your true feelings
Don't make a fool of me, I'm in a good
mood
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.